Luke Fryer

Web Developer

A meticulous web developer with 9+ years of industry experience and a passion for front end web development.

Using the appropriate tools and processes, have created highly performant and visually pleasing websites for clients such as - Walmart, Asda, 188Bet, Coral, Co-op, and Jet2.

Email: luke.fryer.email@gmail.com Portfolio: https://lf20.github.io/

Skills

- Mobile first, UX and Accessibility, Progressive Web Apps, Workflow automation,
- SEO and Semantic code, Site optimisation, HTML Emails, IE7+ Compatibility
- HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, ECMAScript
 6
- Vue.js, Vue CLI, Gridsome
- GSAP, Webpack, Gulp
- Azure Devops, Git, Photoshop, Illustrator,
- Wordpress theme development, Ektron (Certified Administrator)
- Oracle Responsys, Dotmailer, Mailchimp, Salesforce

Experience

Epiphany Search / Front End Developer

May 2018 - Present

Similar role to previous, but with more responsibility. Built many SPA's, and worked closely with back end devs using Umbraco CMS. Further developed my skill set by learning new technologies, processes and workflows.

Home Agency / Front End Developer

Apr 2011 - May 2018, Leeds

Working closely with designers to produce high quality and responsive web projects, with focus on cross-browser compatibility and semantic markup.

Sainsburys / Customer Service Assistant

Sep 2006 - Aug 2010 Leeds

Education

IT Practitioners (General) / Bachelor of Technology (BTech)

2006 - 2008, Leeds College of Technology

Applied ICT / Advanced GCE

2005 - 2006, Leeds College of Technology

Computing (IT Practitioner) / National Diploma

2004 - 2005, Leeds College of Technology